springleap.com 2012-06-22

# Privacy Policy | Springleap.com

Fashion Evolution and all its subsidiaries and associates including springleap (hereafter referred to as "springleap") recognizes that its customers, visitors, users, affiliated companies and others (known collectively or individually as "Users") who use springleap and the services that are offered by springleap (the "Website") value their privacy. This Privacy Policy applies to all of the products, services, and Websites offered by springleap and details important information regarding the use and disclosure of User information collected on the Website.

  * Your use of the Website and any personal information you provide on the Website remains subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the springleap "Terms of Use".
  * Please note that any comment or other content you post or send to the Website becomes published content and is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Policy. Your messages, comments, blogs, content, images, media and other information you make available in public areas of the Springleap website will be seen by people and organizations not related to or controlled by Springleap, and may be used by other parties to make contact with you.
  * Springleap Privacy Policy applies only to Websites and services that are owned and operated by Springleap. While other Websites may be displayed as links from within different areas of the Springleap Website, those sites are owned and operated by other entities, and they may have privacy policies that differ from springleap and the privacy policy that applies to the Website. When linking from Springleap to other websites, if you have privacy concerns, we urge you to review the privacy policies of those sites.

#### 1\. Information Collection and Usage thereof

**General**

  * Springleap does not require that Users register on the Website in order to view its products or User comments. Registration is required to use certain interactive features such as posting comments, participating in the blog forums, and in order to submit ideas, designs, slogans and media (hereafter referred to as "creations") and participate in blogs and competitions as a User who submits, votes or participates in any interactive springleap activities and member interaction.
  * Springleap collects personal information when you register with Springleap, when you visit the Website, when you make a purchase, or any time you provide information to Springleap about yourself and information that relates to you or your interests. Springleap may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from Users, business partners, third party entities or other companies.
  * When you register, we ask for personal information such as your Christian name, surname, email address, and other personally-identifying information (hereafter referred to as "Personal Information"). When you register with Springleap and sign in to our services and competitions, you are not anonymous to springleap.
  * Springleap and the Website automatically receives and records other non-personally-identifying information ("Non-Personal Information") on our server logs from your browser even if you do not register with Springleap, for example, your IP address, Springleap cookie information, and the pages you visit.
  * Springleap uses Non-Personal Information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfil your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

**Children Under 13**

  * Springleap is committed to protecting the privacy of children. Springleap does not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information online from children under the age of 13.
  * If Springleap learns that personally identifiable information of persons under 13 years of age has been collected on Springleap without verified parental or guardian consent, then springleap will take the appropriate steps to delete this information.

#### 2\. Information Sharing and Disclosure

  * Springleap does not rent, sell, or share Personal Information with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

    * We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with Springleap under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your Personal Information to help Springleap communicate with you regarding offers from Springleap, affiliates and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information. Said information and the rights thereto remain the property of Springleap and the right to distribute or use this information is at the discretion of Springleap alone.
    * We provide Non-Personal Information to interested third-parties for purposes of understanding the usage patterns for certain content, services, advertisements, promotions, marketing, publics relations, research and development of future products and services and/or functionality on the Website.
    * Springleap, its affiliates, PR company and marketing partners use both your Personal Information and certain Non-Personal Information to improve the quality, usability, functionality, services and design of the Website and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing User preferences and trends.
    * Springleap may share Personal Information in response to subpoenas, court orders, or other forms of legal process, or to establish or exercise springleap's legal rights or defend against legal claims as well as assist law enforcement entities in the pursuit of meeting the ends of justice as seen fit within the South African Court of law.
    * We may share Personal Information if we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Springleap's Terms of Use, or as otherwise required by law or ordered within a court of law.
    * We may transmit Personal Information if Springleap is acquired by or merged with another company or entity. In this event, Springleap will notify active known users if there is a need to change this Privacy Policy based on an Springleap acquisition or merger. Springleap also retain the right to transmit Personal Information in the process of diluting shares, transferring shares or selling shares to any third party.
    * In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, we may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred, or used furthermore springleap and its shareholders will not be held responsible for the usage, implementation or distribution of the Personal Information.
    * If the Personal Information is stolen or leaked, springleap reserve the right to choose to take every measure they can to track the Personal Information and retrieve the Personal Information as well as prosecute and/or lay charges against the offending parties.
  * Please keep in mind that any personal information, or comments that Users voluntarily disclose on the Website, for example on the blogs, submit pages, commentary, shoutOuts, wordUps, myPage, and others, becomes publicly available. Your account name is displayed to other Users when you send and/or post messages through the Website.

#### 3\. Cookies and Web Beacons

  * Springleap may set and access Springleap cookies on your computer You may. disable these cookies within your browser, but some portions of the Website may require that your Springleap cookies be enabled. Disabling cookies is not recommended by Springleap and Springleap will not entertain assisting in or creating "workarounds" for any problems incurred by Users as a result of disabling cookies within Users' browsers or as a result of the interoperability issues related to security programs such as programs that offer a firewall or other forms of internet security as well as caching programs and programs that claim to improve internet speeds.
  * Springleap lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on Users' computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not springleap's Privacy Policy. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to Springleap's cookies.
  * Springleap may use web beacons in connection with e-mails sent to Springleap users, to let us know whether and when the email was opened. No personal information is transmitted through web beacons.

#### 4\. Confidentiality and Security

  * Springleap uses commercially reasonable technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your Personal Information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any Personal Information you transmit to Springleap and you do so at your own risk. Having said this Springleap reserves the right to sue, chose to assist in the prosecution of and/or take any other legal action that is deemed fit by Springleap and it's legal representatives against the offending parties.
  * Springleap limit access to Personal Information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with Personal Information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. The level of access to Personal Information varies relative to the necessity of the employee's responsibilities and requirements in the process of facilitating their work or meeting their agendas and deadlines prescribed by springleap.

#### 5\. About Editing and Deleting Your Account Information

  * Users can edit their springleap account information at any time by going to their myCrib, myPage, IamMe and personalityMe pages
  * Springleap and it's designated marketing and PR representative reserve the right to use Users' Personal Information in order to send Users certain communications relating to Springleap and springleap services, such as service announcements, and administrative messages, changes that are considered part of Users' Springleap account, without offering the User the opportunity to opt out of receiving them.
  * Users can request Springleap to deactivate their account or notifications. Users can send requests of this nature to deactivate@springleap.com. Requests for account deactivation or Personal Information removal must be accompanied with reasons and pertinent information to those reasons. Springleap reserves the right to reject or facilitate such requests.
  * Springleap reserves the right to deactivate any User account at any time with or without reason or notification.

#### 6\. International Users

If you are a User accessing the Website from the European Union, South Africa, Canada, Australia, Russia, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from South African laws, please be advised that through your continued use of the Website, which is governed by South African law and this Privacy Policy as incorporated in our Terms of Use, you will be transferring your Personal Information into South Africa and you consent to that transfer.

#### 7\. Changes and Updates to this Privacy Policy

Springleap may update this policy at any time in its sole discretion and without prior notice. We will strive to notify you about significant changes in the way we treat Personal Information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Springleap account and/or by placing a notice on the Website. 

#### 8\. Effective Date

This Privacy Policy was last modified 14 February 2008. 

#### 9\. Contact Information

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, you can contact us at:  
Privacy Policy  
Springleap  
161 Gordon Rd, Morningside  
Durban 4001, KZN, South Africa  
privacypolicy@springleap.com
